ACWA Education Department Records 5619/002
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- South Alabama Joint Board - Andalusia, Alabama, 1983 (Box 33, Folder 61)
- South Carolina Coastal Joint Board - James Johnson, 1974-1983 (Box 33, Folder 62)
- Southwest Regional Joint Board (Clothing), 1981-1983 (Box 33, Folder 63)
- Southwestern Ontario Joint Board, 1977-1979 (Box 33, Folder 64)
- Toledo Joint Board, 1969-1978 (Box 33, Folder 65)
- Tidewater Joint Board - Locals #833; 1403; 1622; 1784; 1842; 1896 - Wilton Tyree and Wayne Dernoncourt, 1974-1979 (Box 33, Folder 66)
- Tony Herman - Twin City Joint Board, 1973-1979 (Box 33, Folder 67)
- Upper South Region - Fredericksburg, Virginia, 1983 (Box 33, Folder 68)
- Agreements, 1967-1981 (Box 34, Folder 1)
- Newsletters, 1966-1984 (Box 34, Folder 2)
- Reports, 1939-1985 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  Includes a photographic contact sheet
- General Executive Board Meeting - Tarrytown, New York, 1982 (Box 34, Folder 4)
- Correspondence, 1969-1985 (Box 34, Folder 5)
- Education Department Memos - William Elkuss, 1980-1981 (Box 34, Folder 6)
- Clayola Brown's File - Miscellaneous, 1964-1982 (Box 34, Folder 7)
- Shop Stewards Meeting and Newsletters (I), 1969-1982 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  Includes a collection of black and white photographs
- Shop Stewards Meeting and Newsletters (II), 1973-1980 (Box 35, Folder 2)
- Alton Hodgman - New England Region (TWUA), 1973-1978 (Box 35, Folder 3)
- Frank Cuccio - Dyers and Printers Division, 1973-1978 (Box 35, Folder 4)
- Cotton-Woolen-Worsted-Rayon Division, 1973-1974 (Box 35, Folder 5)
- Celanese Division, 1973-1975 (Box 35, Folder 6)
- Charles Sallee - Regional Director, 1974-1979 (Box 35, Folder 7)
- Midwest Regional Office (Chicago), 1974-1976 (Box 35, Folder 8)
- Local #1896 - Richmond, Virginia, 1975-1979 (Box 35, Folder 9)
- Local #1902 - Geauga Industries, 1974-1978 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  Includes a collection of color photographs of a strike in Middlefield, Ohio and clippings from newspapers covering the strike
- Local 1900 (Oneita) - Andrews and Lane, South Carolina, 1973-1978 (Box 35, Folder 11)
- Local #1933 (GTA) - Maryville, Tennessee, 1975-1979 (Box 35, Folder 12)
- Local #1950 - Belton, South Carolina, 1976-1980 (Box 35, Folder 13)
- Joe Coponi - Quin-State Director, 1973-1981 (Box 35, Folder 14)
- Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, 1973-1976 (Box 35, Folder 15)
- Crest Container Workers - Millville, New Jersey (Quin-State), 1975 (Box 35, Folder 16)
- Norwich Mills, 1973-1975 (Box 35, Folder 17)
- Dayton Program - Locals #199; 21; 48 (Ohio), 1975 (Box 35, Folder 18)
- Quin-State (Organizing), 1974-1978 (Box 35, Folder 19)
- Carol Bush - International Representative, 1974-1975 (Box 35, Folder 20)
- Bruce Dunton (Correspondence TO:), 1973-1981 (Box 35, Folder 21)
- Synthetics Division - Bruce Dunton, 1973-1980 (Box 35, Folder 22)
- AFL-CIO Hobbs Act Information Packet, 1981 (Box 35, Folder 23)
- ACTWU Song Book (Original and Reprint) (Box 35, Folder 24)
  Includes some black and white photographs and some musical notation
- Swedish Delegation, 1983 (Box 35, Folder 25)
  September 20, 1983
- United Nations (Labor Movement) - African Apartheid, 1974-1983 (Box 35, Folder 26)
- South Africa Labour Education Project - (London, England) (SALEP), 1980-1981 (Box 35, Folder 27)
- Portugal (Clay's ACTWU Trip) - Correspondence, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 28)
- Foreign Visitors - Tokyo, Japan, 1979-1982 (Box 35, Folder 29)
- Asian-African Trade Union Visitors (ACTWU), 1983 (Box 35, Folder 30)
  March 28, 1983
- North African Visitors to ACTWU (Women), 1985 (Box 35, Folder 31)
  May 1985
- Foreign Visitors - Columbia (South America), 1980 (Box 35, Folder 32)
  June 30, 1980
- Requests, 1980 (Box 35, Folder 33)
  Includes a black and white copy of a photograph
- Collective Bargaining - "Inside Look" (Discussion Guide Booklet) (Box 35, Folder 34)
- Master Pages - Manual Materials, 1979-1980 (Box 35, Folder 35)
- Master Pages Manuals, 1973-1980 (Box 35, Folder 36)
- Newsletters - Local Unions and Joint Boards, 1979-1983 (Box 35, Folder 37)
  Includes some Spanish language material
- Sol Stetin's Testimonial - Deep South Region - Atlanta, Georgia, 1982 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  February 6, 1982; also includes a collection of black and white copies of photographs
- Bill Elkuss Memorial (ACTWU) (Box 36, Folder 2)
- Wellman Membership Drive - Johnsonville, South Carolina, 1982 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  January 24-30, 1982
- Quin State and New York State Organizers and Managers Conference - Allentown Pennsylvania, 1982 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  February 17-20, 1982; also includes a conference schedule for May 21-22, 1982
- COPE Legislative Institute - Washington, D.C. (Best Western), 1982 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  April 18-23, 1982
- Central North Carolina Joint Board Conference - Greensboro, North Carolina, 1982 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  May 14-15,1982
- Pittsburgh District Joint Board Conference - Indiana University of Pennsylvania, 1981-1982 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  Covers the August 12-15, 1982 conference; also includes a conference schedule from 1981
- Deep South Regional Joint Board Conference (Raynor), 1982 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  August 27-29, 1982
- Southern Regional Joint Board Conference (Clothing) - Knoxville, Tennessee, 1982 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  October 15-16, 1982
- Pennsylvania Joint board Conference (Pete Swoboda) - Lebanon, Pennsylvania, 1982 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  August 13-14, 1982
- Synthetic and Upper South Division Conference - George Meany Labor Studies Center, 1982 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  May 2-7, 1982
- Central Alabama-Georgia Joint Board Leadership Training Conference - Columbus, Georgia, 1982 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  July 22-24, 1982
- Administrative Classes (Raynor and Dunton/Rogin and Rachlin) - Washington, D.C., 1982 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  August 1-4, 1982
- Mid-South Regional Joint Board Meeting - Myrtle Beach, South Carolina, 1982 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  December 4-5, 1982
- Canadian-USA Studies: The Johns Hopkins University - Washington, D.C., 1981-1982 (Box 36, Folder 15)
- Miscellaneous Conferences, 1980-1983 (Box 36, Folder 16)
- Southern Summer School (Textile) - East Tennessee State University - Johnson City, Tennessee, 1979 (Box 36, Folder 17)
  August 26-31, 1979; includes a black and white photograph of the participants
- Summer Schools, 1979-1983 (Box 36, Folder 18)
- Summer Schools/Regional Conferences, 1960-1984 (Box 36, Folder 19)
  Includes some English-French material
- Regional Conferences/Schools, 1974-1979 (Box 36, Folder 20)
- Teaching Outline, 1984 (Box 36, Folder 21)
- NAACP Convention, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 22)
  June 23-27, 1985; includes clippings from newspapers covering the convention
- Civil Rights, 1987-1988 (Box 36, Folder 23)
- Labor Development in the Caribbean and South America, 1983-1986 (Box 36, Folder 24)
- Labor Law Reform, 1977-1985 (Box 36, Folder 25)
  Includes summaries of the Wagner Act (1935) and the Taft-Hartley Act (1947)
- Miscellany: Governance, Boycotts, and Newsletters, 1984-1990 (Box 36, Folder 26)
- Newsletter Packets I, 1978-1987 (Box 37, Folder 1)
- Newsletter Packets II, 1980-1989 (Box 37, Folder 2)
- Correspondence - Joint Boards/Districts, 1981-1988 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  Includes two collections of black and white photographs and several photographic contact sheets
- ACTWU Departments and Education Staff, 1984-1988 (Box 37, Folder 4)
- Miscellaneous, 1973-1988 (Box 37, Folder 5)
- Sol Stetin's Correspondence, 1973-1981 (Box 37, Folder 6)
- Correspondence (Bruce Raynor, Clayola Brown, and Sol Stetin), 1973-1987 (Box 38, Folder 1)
- Miscellaneous, 1973-1988 (Box 38, Folder 2)
- 1984 Regional Conferences, 1983-1984 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  Includes a black and white photograph of the 1984 COPE School
- 1985 Regional Conferences, 1984-1985 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  Includes a collection of black and white photographs and a color photograph
- 1986 Regional Conferences, 1985-1986 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  Includes a collection of color photographs, black and white photographs, and several photographic negatives
- 1987 Regional Conferences (Box 38, Folder 6)
  Includes a color photograph
- 1988 Regional Conferences (Box 38, Folder 7)
  Includes a black and white photograph
- Resolution on Foreign Policy (Box 38, Folder 8)
- Statement on Economic Policy (Box 38, Folder 9)
- Resolution on the Legislative Needs of Working People (Box 38, Folder 10)
- Resolution on Civil Liberties (Box 38, Folder 11)
- Resolution on Civil Rights (Box 38, Folder 12)
- Coretta King Statement to the Martin Luther King Jr. Holiday Commission - Washington D.C., 1985 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  March 25, 1985
- Dream keepers (Dave Howell News Director), 1984 (Box 39, Folder 2)
- Martin Luther King Medallion, 1986 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  Includes a color photograph of a MLK Memorial Medallion
- Letters from Appointees/International Presidents Concerning the Martin Luther King Jr. Federal Holiday Commission, 1985 (Box 39, Folder 4)
- Reports, Minutes, Summaries, 1985-1986 (Box 39, Folder 5)
- By-Laws, Resolutions, Articles, 1984 (Box 39, Folder 6)
- Files on the Martin Luther King Jr. Holiday Commission, 1984-1987 (Box 39, Folder 7)
- Apartheid Boycott - (South Africa Special Project), 1986 (Box 39, Folder 8)
- Commission on Civil Rights - Washington D.C., 1982 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  Statement of the United States Commission on Civil Rights on School Desegregation, December 1982
- AFL-CIO Civil Rights Conference Resolutions Committee - Omni Hotel, Baltimore, 1986 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  July 1, 1986
- Civil Rights Correspondence, 1982-1986 (Box 39, Folder 11)
- Civil Rights, 1979-1985 (Box 39, Folder 12)
- Civil Rights - General, 1965-1981 (Box 39, Folder 13)
- Busing, 1972-1975 (Box 39, Folder 14)
  Includes newspaper clippings
- A. Philip Randolph Conference - Dallas, Texas, 1985-1986 (Box 39, Folder 15)
  September 5-8, 1985
- Civil Rights Conference - AFL-CIO Headquarters, 1985-1986 (Box 39, Folder 16)
  July 25, 1985
- Civil Liberties, 1979-1981 (Box 39, Folder 17)
- Urban League Conference - Washington D.C., 1985 (Box 39, Folder 18)
  July 23, 1985
- Civil Rights Conference - George Meany Labor Studies Center, 1985 (Box 39, Folder 19)
  April 21-25, 1985
- NAACP Convention - Dallas, Texas, 1984-1985 (Box 39, Folder 20)
  June 23-27, 1985
- Caribbean Basin and FITIVCC, 1985-1986 (Box 39, Folder 21)
  FITIVCC stands for the Interamerican Textile, Leather, Garment, and Shoe Workers Federation
- Locals/Regions Correspondence, 1970-1980 (Box 39, Folder 22)
- Correspondence I, 1975-1979 (Box 39, Folder 23)
- Correspondence II, 1980-1989 (Box 39, Folder 24)
  Includes a color photograph and several copies of black and white photographs
- Wagner Labor Archives (Box 40, Folder 1)
- Shop Steward Cartoons - Labor Unity, 1986-1991 (Box 40, Folder 2)
- Linking the Locals (The Joint Board) (Box 40, Folder 3)
- Resolutions (Box 40, Folder 4)
- Mailings - ACTWU Affiliates, 1985-1989 (Box 40, Folder 5)
- Membership Drives Report (For Sol Stetin), 1974-1987 (Box 40, Folder 6)
- Local #2398 - Membership Drive - Johnsonville, South Carolina, 1982 (Box 40, Folder 7)
- National Council of Negro Women, 1984-1987 (Box 40, Folder 8)
- NAACP, 1975-1987 (Box 40, Folder 9)
- The Martin Luther King Jr. Center, 1986-1987 (Box 40, Folder 10)
- Miscellany, 1973-1990 (Box 40, Folder 11)
- TWUA-ACWUA Merger, 1975-1976 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  Includes newspaper clippings and handwritten notes
- King Activity Celebration, 1987 (Box 40, Folder 13)
- National Textile Recruitment and Training Program, 1976-1980 (Box 40, Folder 14)
- OSHA Education and Training Grant, 1980-1990 (Box 40, Folder 15)
- National Endowment for the Humanities, 1974-1977 (Box 40, Folder 16)
- Klu Klux Klan/Right Wing Group, 1980-1982 (Box 40, Folder 17)
- Leaflets (Flyers), 1977-1982 (Box 40, Folder 18)
- International Affairs, 1973-1989 (Box 40, Folder 19)
- Ed Bruzgul (Intern), 1976-1977 (Box 40, Folder 20)
- Sidney Hillman Award Recipients, 1979-1989 (Box 40, Folder 21)
- Bingham Graves, 1978-1981 (Box 40, Folder 22)
- Elkuss' Memorial, 1982-1983 (Box 40, Folder 23)
- Footwear Press Conference, 1984 (Box 40, Folder 24)
  January 24, 1984
- Conferences and Training Programs, 1980-1988 (Box 40, Folder 25)
- Grievances, Reports, and Memos, 1985-1986 (Box 40, Folder 26)
- Agreements, 1979-1987 (Box 40, Folder 27)
- Newsletters and Flyers, 1985-1988 (Box 40, Folder 28)
- Local Union Finder (Box 40, Folder 29)
- J.P. Stevens and Company - Wallace, North Carolina - Case Number 11-RD-405, 1985 (Box 40, Folder 30)
- Drug Testing - Ohio State - Arbitration Cases, 1981-1986 (Box 40, Folder 31)
- News Clippings, 1983-1985 (Box 40, Folder 32)
  Includes scanned copies of news articles and news clippings pasted onto sheets of paper
- Attendance Report (Blank) (Box 41, Folder 1)
- FITTVCC/ORI Letterheads (Box 41, Folder 2)
- ACTWU (International Solidarity) Attachments (Box 41, Folder 3)
- Attendance 1994 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  January-March 1994
- Attendance Report 1993, 1993-1994 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  January 1993 to January 1, 1994
- Bills and Vouchers - Finance, 1992-1994 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  some Spanish language materials; includes scanned copies of checks
- Airline Reservations - Elisa Hubbard, 1994 (Box 41, Folder 7)
- Airline Reservations, 1993 (Box 41, Folder 8)
- Express Mail Receipts, 1991-1994 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  Some English/Spanish material
- Expense Report, 1994 (Box 41, Folder 10)
- Expense Reports (La Luz), 1992-1993 (Box 41, Folder 11)
- Fax Verification, 1993-1994 (Box 41, Folder 12)
- Fax Verification Copies, 1991-1993 (Box 41, Folder 13)
- Incoming Correspondence, 1993 (Box 41, Folder 14)
- Outgoing Correspondence, 1993-1994 (Box 41, Folder 15)
- Correspondence Jose La Luz, 1993 (Box 41, Folder 16)
  Includes some Spanish language materials
- Interoffice Correspondence, 1989-1993 (Box 41, Folder 17)
- Request for Stationary and Supplies, 1993-1994 (Box 41, Folder 18)
- Telephone Receipts, 1993-1994 (Box 41, Folder 19)
- Visitors File, 1993 (Box 41, Folder 20)
  Mostly Spanish language material
- Jack Sheinkman, 1994 (Box 41, Folder 21)
- Jack Sheinkman - President, 1989-1993 (Box 41, Folder 22)
  Includes some Spanish language material; also includes news clippings
- John Hudson - Headwear Division - New York-New Jersey Joint Board, 1991-1993 (Box 41, Folder 23)
- Communications (Jo-Ann Mort), 1993 (Box 41, Folder 24)
- Economic Affairs (Ron Blackwell), 1992-1993 (Box 41, Folder 25)
- Finance (Charlie Danitz), 1990-1993 (Box 41, Folder 26)
- Training Local Union Educators, 1990 (Box 41, Folder 27)
- International Solidarity, 1993 (Box 41, Folder 28)
  Drafted international solidarity resolutions with editors' marks and revisions; includes a floppy disk
- International Solidarity (Jose La Luz), 1984-1994 (Box 41, Folder 29)
- Legislative-Public Affairs (Liz Smith), 1989-1993 (Box 41, Folder 30)
  Includes two copies of a black and white photograph
- Operations (Dale Marshall), 1989-1994 (Box 41, Folder 31)
- Address Changes, 1993 (Box 41, Folder 32)
- Political Action - Local (Nick Unger), 1993-1994 (Box 41, Folder 33)
- Research (Keir Jorgensen), 1989-1993 (Box 41, Folder 34)
- Industrial (Harry Lautman), 1993 (Box 41, Folder 35)
- ACTWU on NAFTA, 1993 (Box 41, Folder 36)
- AFL-CIO, 1990-1993 (Box 41, Folder 37)
- After NAFTA - Political Reports, 1993 (Box 41, Folder 38)
- Clinton's NAFTA, 1993 (Box 41, Folder 39)
  Includes news clippings
- Economic Reports (Spanish), 1993 (Box 41, Folder 40)
  Entirely Spanish language materials
- NAFTA/Global Production, 1992-1993 (Box 41, Folder 41)
- NAFTA/Immigration Issues, 1993 (Box 41, Folder 42)
  Includes news clippings and some Spanish language material
- Mexico General, 1991-1993 (Box 41, Folder 43)
- Participation Hispanic Organizations, 1991-1993 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  Includes some English/Spanish material; includes also news clippings
- NAFTA News Articles, 1991-1993 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  Includes some Spanish language materials; includes news clippings
- Public Officials and NAFTA, 1993 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  Includes some Spanish language material; includes news clippings
- Reports on NAFTA, 1992-1993 (Box 42, Folder 4)
- US-Mexico Free Trade Agreement (Spanish), 1990-1993 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  Entirely Spanish language material; includes news clippings
- Testimonies, 1991-1992 (Box 42, Folder 6)
- ACTWU Participation - NAFTA, 1991 (Box 42, Folder 7)
- Agriculture/NAFTA, 1992 (Box 42, Folder 8)
- Boycott, 1991 (Box 42, Folder 9)
- Canada-US Free Trade Agreement, 1990-1991 (Box 42, Folder 10)
- NAFTA: Caribbean Basin (General), 1993 (Box 42, Folder 11)
- Cuauhtmoc Cardenas, 1990-1993 (Box 42, Folder 12)
- Comision Mexicana de Defensa y Promocion de los Derechos Humanos (English), 1991 (Box 42, Folder 13)
  Document is in English; the translation of the organization's name is Mexican Commission for the Defense and Promotion of Human Rights
- Congress of the United States of America, 1991 (Box 42, Folder 14)
- Development and Trade Strategies for North America, 1991-1992 (Box 42, Folder 15)
- Economic Policy Institute, 1991-1993 (Box 42, Folder 16)
- Education and NAFTA, 1991-1992 (Box 42, Folder 17)
- Exploiting Both Sides, 1991 (Box 42, Folder 18)
- Japan/Mexico Free Trade Agreement, 1991 (Box 42, Folder 19)
- Maquiladoras, 1987-1993 (Box 42, Folder 20)
- Matamoros/Agapito Gonzalez, 1991-1992 (Box 43, Folder 1)
- Mexico/Environment, 1991-1993 (Box 43, Folder 2)
- Newsletter Articles, 1990-1993 (Box 43, Folder 3)
- NAFTA: Newspaper Articles, 1989-1993 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  Includes news clippings; includes some Spanish language material
- Other Resources Available, 1991-1993 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  Includes a postcard with a black and white photograph
- NAFTA/Who Benefits?, 1991-1993 (Box 43, Folder 6)
- United States of Mexico Official Packet for the Public, 1991-1992 (Box 43, Folder 7)
- Remarks by Jack Sheinkman, 1990-1993 (Box 43, Folder 8)
- Press Releases, 1992 (Box 43, Folder 9)
- Objectives - Preliminary Negotiating, 1991-1992 (Box 43, Folder 10)
- Reports Free Trade, 1989-1993 (Box 43, Folder 11)
- Statements, 1991-1992 (Box 43, Folder 12)
- United States Senate, 1991-1993 (Box 43, Folder 13)
- Women and NAFTA, 1988-1993 (Box 43, Folder 14)
  Includes English/Spanish material
- US-Mexico-Canada Free Trade Agreement Talks, 1990-1993 (Box 43, Folder 15)
  Includes some French language material
- US/Mexico Free Trade Agreement (Confidential), 1990-1992 (Box 43, Folder 16)
  Includes some Spanish language material; includes some French language material; includes news clippings
- Jose La Luz - Participation on NAFTA - Press, 1992-1993 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  Includes some Spanish language material and English/Spanish material; includes news clippings
- Jose La Luz's Participation - NAFTA Agendas, 1991-1993 (Box 44, Folder 2)
- United States/Mexico, 1989-1990 (Box 44, Folder 3)
- NAFTA, 1992 (Box 44, Folder 4)
- US-Mexico Free Trade Agreement (Confidential 1992) (Box 44, Folder 5)
- The Bulletin Newsletter, 1993 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  October 1993
- Wonker Education Manual, 1992 (Box 44, Folder 7)
- Education Update - Union Yes, 1993 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  November 1993
- Highlander Reports, 1993 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  October-December 1993
- Labor Unity Newsletter, 1993 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  September-October 1993
- Latin American Labor News, 1992-1993 (Box 44, Folder 11)
  Includes some articles published in Spanish
- La Voz Latina (Labor Council for Latin American Advancement), 1993 (Box 44, Folder 12)
  September 1993
- Local 1199 - Newsletter/Magazine, 1993-1994 (Box 44, Folder 13)
- Outlook Newsletter, 1993 (Box 44, Folder 14)
- Teamster - Magazine, 1993 (Box 44, Folder 15)
  December 1993
- World of Work, 1993 (Box 44, Folder 16)
- Outlook - Newsletter (American Institute for Free Labor Development), 1993 (Box 44, Folder 17)
- Center for Immigrant Rights, 1993 (Box 44, Folder 18)
  January 1993
- Democratic Socialists of America, 1991-1992 (Box 44, Folder 19)
- Democratic Socialists of America, 1993 (Box 44, Folder 20)
- The Americas Project/DSA, 1992 (Box 44, Folder 21)
- Mr. Pat Lacefield - Democratic Socialists of America, 1990 (Box 44, Folder 22)
- Democratic Left, 1990 (Box 44, Folder 23)
- Ethnic Labor Coalition, 1991-1992 (Box 44, Folder 24)
- Hispanic Labor Council, 1990-1993 (Box 44, Folder 25)
- Hearing on the American Labor Movement by Jack Sheinkman, 1992 (Box 44, Folder 26)
  December 9, 1992
- Puerto Rican/Hispanic Taskforce, 1993 (Box 44, Folder 27)
- Labor Council for Latin American Advancement, 1980-1993 (Box 44, Folder 28)
  Includes English/Spanish material; includes some Spanish language material
- Latinos in the US and NAFTA, 1991-1993 (Box 44, Folder 29)
- Midwest/Northeast Voter Registration Education Project, 1989-1992 (Box 44, Folder 30)
- The Midwest Center for Labor Research - Labor Research Review, 1993-1994 (Box 44, Folder 31)
- NAFTA (Confidential), 1992-1993 (Box 44, Folder 32)
- Paolo Freire's Conference, 1991 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  December 5-7, 1991, entitled "Challenging Education, Creating Alliances"
- US, Mexico, and Puerto Rico, 1991-1992 (Box 45, Folder 2)
- SVRI (Southwest Voter Registration Institute), 1991-1992 (Box 45, Folder 3)
- Political Endorsements, 1990-1991 (Box 45, Folder 4)
- N.D.P (New Democratic Party), 1993 (Box 45, Folder 5)
- NCLR (National Council of La Raza), 1991 (Box 45, Folder 6)
- Puerto Rico Labor Organizations (Spanish), 1991-1992 (Box 46, Folder 1)
- Puerto Rico Labor Movement, 1989-1992 (Box 46, Folder 2)
- Puerto Rico's Economy, 1991-1992 (Box 46, Folder 3)
- Statement of ACTWU on Section 936, 1993 (Box 46, Folder 4)
- ACTWU's Position on Section 936 (Spanish), 1993 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  Almost entirely Spanish language material; includes news clippings
- Congress/Section 936, 1992-1993 (Box 46, Folder 6)
- Puerto Rico Labor Movement - 936 Reform Campaign, 1991-1993 (Box 46, Folder 7)
- Puerto Rico Section 936 - News Articles, 1992-1993 (Box 46, Folder 8)
- Argentina Labor Movement, 1992-1993 (Box 46, Folder 9)
- Bolivia, 1993 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  Entirely Spanish language material
- Brussels, Belgium (International Textile, Garment and Leather Workers' Federation), 1993 (Box 46, Folder 11)
- Ericson Crivelli (CUT Brazil), 1993 (Box 46, Folder 12)
- CLC (Canadian Labour Congress), 1993 (Box 46, Folder 13)
  Includes English/French material
- Central America Project (Donna Mandel), 1993 (Box 46, Folder 14)
- Adozona (Principles), 1993 (Box 46, Folder 15)
- American Institute for Free Labor Development/Dominican Republic, 1993 (Box 46, Folder 16)
- Confederacion Nacional de Trabajadores Dominicanos/Dominican Republic, 1994 (Box 46, Folder 17)
- Confederacion Trabajadores Unitaria/Dominican Republic, 1993 (Box 46, Folder 18)
- Central Unitoria de Trabajadores Dominicanos/Dominican Republic, 1991 (Box 46, Folder 19)
- Frente Continental de Organizaciones Comunales - Dominican Republic, 1992 (Box 46, Folder 20)
- General System of Preferences - Sub-Committee, 1993 (Box 46, Folder 21)
- International Confederation of Free Trade Unions/Dominican Republic, 1993 (Box 46, Folder 22)
- Levi's (Dominican Republic), 1993 (Box 46, Folder 23)
- Honduras Labor Movement, 1992-1994 (Box 46, Folder 24)
- News Articles (Spanish) - Dominican Republic, 1993-1994 (Box 46, Folder 25)
- Articles - Dominican Republic, 1993 (Box 46, Folder 26)
- European Popular and Labor Organizations, 1992-1993 (Box 46, Folder 27)
- CUSG, 1992 (Box 46, Folder 28)
- Haiti, 1986 (Box 46, Folder 29)
  June 13, 1986
- International Labor Standards, 1993 (Box 46, Folder 30)
- Cuauhtmoc Cardenas, 1992-1993 (Box 46, Folder 31)
  Includes mostly Spanish language material
- Friedrich Egert Stiftung Foundation (Mexico), 1993-1994 (Box 46, Folder 32)
- National Rainbow Coalition, 1993 (Box 46, Folder 33)
- South African Clothing and Textile Worker's Union (SACTWU), 1991-1994 (Box 46, Folder 34)
- FITTVCC/ORI, 1993-1994 (Box 46, Folder 35)